<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Weekend Of Dreams tracker</title>
    <link href="https://github.io/muirio/wod/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://github.io/muirio/wod" />
    <updated>2021-03-02T08:28:37+00:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>James M</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://github.io/muirio/wod</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Infringements</title>
        <author>
            <name>James M</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://github.io/muirio/wod/infringements/"/>
        <id>https://github.io/muirio/wod/infringements/</id>

        <updated>2021-03-01T21:50:21+00:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Twatstitution</title>
        <author>
            <name>James M</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://github.io/muirio/wod/twatstitution/"/>
        <id>https://github.io/muirio/wod/twatstitution/</id>

        <updated>2021-03-01T22:19:46+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    We the People of the United Twatdom of Twatland, in order to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="chat-row">
<div class="chat-bubble-contents" title="Mon, 1 Mar 2021 22:05">
<p class="chat-body msg msg--success msg--highlight ">We the People of the United Twatdom of Twatland, in order to form a more perfect Union, establish Justice, ensure domestic Tranquility, provide for the common defence, promote the general Welfare, and secure the Blessings of Liberty to ourselves and our kindred brethren, do ordain and establish this Twatstitution for the United Twatdom of Twatland.</p>
<hr>
<h2>Schedule I - Legislative</h2>
</div>
<h3 title="Mon, 1 Mar 2021 22:05"><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Article I - Twat Shot Nominations</span></h3>
<p>To receive a twat shot one must behave like a ‘twat’. Upon behaving like a ‘twat’, any member of the Commons may ‘nominate’ the offender for a twat shot. Nominations must be supported by two other members of the House. Following a nomination, the support of the House must be acquired within a 24 hour period.</p>
<div data-push-iden="ujEV75KHsU8sjzl7esaOsK"> </div>
<h3 class="chat-bubble left" data-push-iden="ujEV75KHsU8sjzl7esaOsK"><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Article II - Twatute of Limitations</span></h3>
<p>Twat behaviour has the right to be forgiven therefore all behaviour is subject to the ‘Twatute of Limitations’ whereby previous behaviour can no longer be punished.</p>
<p><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">The Twatute of Limitations is an unfixed period, but common law suggests the time be reasonable given the circumstances of the alleged twat breach e.g </span><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">if on a night out, a nomination the following day is likely to be con- sidered acceptable, however, if everyone is sober then a couple of hours would be more appropriate.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Article III - Twat Shot Disputes</span></h3>
<p><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">A judged twat has the right to appeal. During the appeal process, the de- fendant has the right to present evidence to the assembled court to try and overturn a ruling. All disputes will be settled by the Speaker of the Commons. The defendant has 24 hours to prepare their case. The defendant has the right to be exempt from further incrimination during the appeal process (although this is not exhaustive to all admissions dur- ing this time, and any attempt to use this as such is seen as a breach of the faith). Failure to overturn a twat shot results in the doubling of the punishment for the defendant.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Article IV - Double Twatardy</span></h3>
<p><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">No member of the commons may be punished twice for the same incident. This is not to say that you can not receive multiple punishments for a given incident but these should be dealt with in a singular judgement session.</span></p>
</div>
<div class="chat-row">
<div class="chat-bubble left" data-push-iden="ujEV75KHsU8sjBleqkQuhU">
<div class="chat-bubble-contents" title="Mon, 1 Mar 2021 22:06">
<p class="chat-body">Double Twatardy does not limit twat shots from being given for repeated offences of a similar nature, nor does it limit the re-opening of the case if new information comes to light.</p>
<h3>Article V - The Bell Test</h3>
<p>It is impossible for the House to ensure all loopholes are closed. As such a simple Bell Test is applied to any arising cases that highlight loopholes within the Twatstitution.</p>
<h3>Article VI - Amendments to the Twatstitution</h3>
<p>Anyone can propose an amendment to the Twatstitution. Amendments must be agreed by the Speaker and then the House has 24 hours to lodge a concern to the amendment. If no concerns are raided the amendment passes. If the Speaker rejects the amendment no further action is required. If a member of the House raises a concern an open forum will be launched where all present members will be given the option to vote. All choices re- quire a majority from the House.</p>
<h3>Article VII - Suspension of Twat Nominations</h3>
<p>Before the start of any ‘Weekend of Dreams’, all twat shot nominations will be suspended for 24 hours prior to the event. This is to avoid mass nominations and allow the Speaker chance to formalise the list.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="chat-row">
<div class="chat-bubble left" data-push-iden="ujEV75KHsU8sjEA3oCBPga">
<div class="chat-bubble-contents" title="Mon, 1 Mar 2021 22:06">
<p class="chat-body">Suspension of nominations is not an excuse for twattish behaviour. Behaviour during this period can be nominated once the Weekend of Dreams commences.</p>
<h3>Article VIII - Clearing Twat Shots</h3>
<p>All twat shots must be cleared by the end of the nearest Weekend of Dreams. When clearing a twat shot, an apology must be offered to the group from the offender for their behaviour demonstrating that they have grown. All twat shots must be at least a singular shot of a highly alcoholic bever- age. Twat shots cannot be cleared at a ‘small gathering’ no matter how many members of the commons are present. It must be at a Weekend of Dreams.</p>
<p class="msg msg--info">The exception to <a href="http://9.0.0.4/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">9.4</a> is that a twat shot offence which occurs during a small gathering can be cleared instantly during the gathering.</p>
<p>A twat shot can never be cleared or removed for good behaviour. Good behaviour and bad behaviour are separate issues handled in different ways.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="chat-row">
<div class="chat-bubble left" data-push-iden="ujEV75KHsU8sjzXtzfYY7o">
<div class="chat-bubble-contents" title="Mon, 1 Mar 2021 22:06">
<h2 class="chat-body">Schedule II</h2>
<h3>Executive Article I - Speaker of the House</h3>
<p>The Speaker of the House is regarded as the highest honour within the Commons and should be regarded as such by all members. Failure to recognise the authority of the Speaker will result in a twat shot. The Speaker of the House is elected at the end of each Weekend of Dreams. It is assumed that the Speaker of the House will run unopposed in the majority of cases.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Countdown</title>
        <author>
            <name>James M</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://github.io/muirio/wod/weekend-of-dreams-tracker/"/>
        <id>https://github.io/muirio/wod/weekend-of-dreams-tracker/</id>

        <updated>2021-03-02T08:28:37+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     The next WOD is planned for October 21 2021, which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p id="the-next-wod-is-planned-for-october-21-2021-which-is">
    The next WOD is planned for October 21 2021, which is
  </p>
<div>
</div>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
